Finding Aid for the Louis Jolyon West Papers LSC.0590
UCLA Library Special Collections
- 7. Research Files., 1890-1996.
  - 7.2 Cults., 1942-1996.
    - Sedona Institute., undated. (Box 237, Folder 5)
    - Seed, The., 1973, 1990. (Box 237, Folder 6)
    - Self-Realization Fellowship., 1985, 1992. (Box 237, Folder 7)
    - Shepherding., 1981, 1984. (Box 237, Folder 8)
    - Shoresh Yishai., undated. (Box 237, Folder 9)
    - Sikhs., 1981, 1984-1986. (Box 237, Folder 10)
    - Simmonds, Robert B.., 1977, 1984. (Box 237, Folder 11)
    - Singer, Margaret Thaler., 1979. (Box 237, Folder 12)
    - "Sizzler Group"/Daniel Donnovan., undated. (Box 237, Folder 13)
    - Skinheads., 1989, 1991. (Box 237, Folder 14)
    - Sorting It Out (Berkeley 1981)., 1980. (Box 237, Folder 15)
    - Southern California Psychiatric Society., 1984. (Box 237, Folder 16)
    - Springs of Living Water., undated. (Box 237, Folder 17)
    - Stonegate., undated. (Box 237, Folder 18)
    - Stop Abuse by Counselors., 1976, 1981, 1983-1984, 1986-1987, 1990-1991, 1993. (Box 237, Folder 19)
    - Subud meditation., 1987-1988. (Box 238, Folder 1)
    - Sufism/Sufi Muslim., 1974-1975, 1982, 1989, 1991, 1993. (Box 238, Folder 2)
    - Sullin, Paul., 1989-1990. (Box 238, Folder 3)
    - Sullivanians/Sullivanism movement (1 of 2)., 1975, 1983-1984, 1986-1987. (Box 238, Folder 4)
    - Sullivanians/Sullivanism movement (2 of 2)., 1986. (Box 238, Folder 5)
      Contains VHS tape.
    - Summit workshops., 1980-1981, 1983-1984. (Box 238, Folder 6)
    - SYDA Foundation (Muktananda/Nityananda)., 1981-1983. (Box 238, Folder 7)
    - Synanon., 1980-1986, 1992. (Box 238, Folder 8)
    - Szimhart, Joe., 1984, 1991-1993. (Box 239, Folder 1)
    - Tara Center., 1982. (Box 239, Folder 2)
    - Temple Aviv Judea., undated. (Box 239, Folder 3)
    - Temple of Set., 1976, 1980-1981, 1983, 1986, 1993. (Box 239, Folder 4)
    - Temple of the Divine Mother., undated. (Box 239, Folder 5)
    - Theosophy., 1990. (Box 239, Folder 6)
    - Three in One Concepts., 1995. (Box 239, Folder 7)
    - Trachtman, Rabbi., 1983. (Box 239, Folder 8)
    - Transcendental Meditation (TM)., 1975, 1985-1987, 1989-1992, 1994. (Box 239, Folder 9)
    - Trumpet of Truth., 1982. (Box 239, Folder 10)
    - UCLA., 1984-1985, 1993. (Box 239, Folder 11)
    - UCLA interest., 1984. (Box 239, Folder 12)
    - Unbound, Inc.., 1988. (Box 239, Folder 13)
    - Unification Church--Organization and Steven A. Hassan press conference statement., 1985. (Box 239, Folder 14)
    - Unification Church--Friedrich W. Haack, "Unification Church Connections," WMC Munich., 1987. (Box 239, Folder 15)
    - Unification Church--Barbara Underwood Scharff, "Voluntary Deprogramming with Consent"., undated. (Box 239, Folder 16)
    - Unification Church--International Conference on the Unity of Sciences (ICUS)., 1978-1979, 1980-1981, 1987-1988. (Box 239, Folder 17)
    - Unification Church--Legal affairs (1 of 3)., 1979-1981, 1983. (Box 239, Folder 18)
    - Unification Church--Legal affairs (2 of 3)., 1977-1978, 1980. (Box 240, Folder 1)
    - Unification Church--Legal affairs (3 of 3)., 1981. (Box 240, Folder 2)
    - Unification Church-Newsletters and printed materials., 1973, 1975-1977, 1981, 1984-1987. (Box 240, Folder 3)
    - Unification Church--News clippings (1 of 2)., 1973-1991. (Box 240, Folder 4)
    - Unification Church--News clippings (2 of 2)., 1973-1991. (Box 240, Folder 5)
    - Unification Church--D. Kelley/National Council of Churches of Christ., 1984, 1987. (Box 240, Folder 6)
    - Unification Church--The Collegiate Association for the Research of Principles (C.A.R.P.)., 1979, 1981-1982, 1984. (Box 240, Folder 7)
    - Unification Church--"Ticket to Heaven" movie., 1981. (Box 240, Folder 8)
    - Unity-In-Diversity., 1980, 1982. (Box 240, Folder 9)
    - Universal Life Church., undated. (Box 240, Folder 10)
    - University Bible Fellowship., 1980-1981, 1983-1984, 1991, 1996-1997. (Box 240, Folder 11)
    - Vatican Report., 1986. (Box 240, Folder 12)
    - Vineyard Fellowship/John Wimber., 1990. (Box 240, Folder 13)
    - Watchman Fellowship, Inc.., 1992. (Box 240, Folder 14)
    - Way International, The., 1978-1982, 1985. (Box 240, Folder 15)
    - We Care Ministries., undated. (Box 240, Folder 16)
    - Weisner, Thomas S. paper., 1986. (Box 241, Folder 1)
    - Wellspring/Paul Martin., 1989-1993. (Box 241, Folder 2)
    - West Los Angeles Capital of the Age of Enlightenment., undated. (Box 241, Folder 3)
      See also "Jai Guru Dev"
    - Whitaker, Terry Cole Ministries., 1983-1985. (Box 241, Folder 4)
    - Williamson, Marianne/A Course in Miracles., 1992. (Box 241, Folder 5)
    - Wilshire, David., undated. (Box 241, Folder 6)
    - Wingspread Conference: "Cultism: A Conference for Scholars and Policy Makers"--Planning materials (1 of 2)., 1980, 1982-1985. (Box 241, Folder 7)
      Conference sponsored by the American Family Foundation, Neuropsychiatric Institute at UCLA, and The Johnson Foundation. Conference scheduled for 1985 September 9-11.
    - Wingspread Conference: "Cultism: A Conference for Scholars and Policy Makers"--Planning materials (2 of 2)., 1981, 1984-1985. (Box 241, Folder 8)
    - Wingspread Conference: "Cultism: A Conference for Scholars and Policy Makers"--Folders and materials., 1980-1985. (Box 241, Folder 9)
    - Wingspread Conference: "Cultism: A Conference for Scholars and Policy Makers"--Wingspread report mailings., 1985-1986. (Box 241, Folder 10)
    - Wingspread Conference: "Cultism: A Conference for Scholars and Policy Makers"--Report., 1975, 1977-1985. (Box 242, Folder 1)
    - Wingspread Conference: "Cultism: A Conference for Scholars and Policy Makers"--Post-conference responses., 1982, 1986. (Box 242, Folder 2)
    - Wingspread Conference: "Cultism: A Conference for Scholars and Policy Makers"--Invitations and response correspondence., 1984-1987. (Box 242, Folder 3)
    - Wingspread Conference: "Cultism: A Conference for Scholars and Policy Makers"--Press Conference (1985 September 11)., 1982, 1984-1985. (Box 242, Folder 4)
    - Wingspread Conference: "Cultism: A Conference for Scholars and Policy Makers"--Harrassment., 1955, 1973, 1979, 1981, 1985-1986. (Box 242, Folder 5)
    - Wingspread Conference: "Cultism: A Conference for Scholars and Policy Makers"--Support for conference correspondence., 1981, 1983-1985. (Box 242, Folder 6)
    - Word of Life., 1990, 1992. (Box 242, Folder 7)
    - World Evangelization, Inc.., undated. (Box 242, Folder 8)
    - Worldwide Church of God/Armstrong., 1972, 1979-1982, 1985. (Box 243, Folder 1)
    - Yahwah Ben Yahwah., 1992. (Box 243, Folder 2)
    - YMI., 1979. (Box 243, Folder 3)
    - Zendik Society., 1982, 1984. (Box 243, Folder 4)
    - Zerin, Marjory Fisher., 1983. (Box 243, Folder 5)
    - "Cults, violence and the media" negatives and slides (oversized box)., 1984 May 4. (Box 249, Folder 1)
  - 7.3 Newspaper clippings., 1943-1984.
    - Age., 1977-1978, 1980. (Box 243, Folder 6)
    - Alcohol and Alcoholism., 1975, 1979-1982. (Box 243, Folder 7)
    - Alcohol and Alcoholism--Violence., 1979. (Box 243, Folder 8)
    - Alcohol and Alcoholism--Research., 1977-1980, 1982. (Box 243, Folder 9)
    - Alcohol and Alcoholism--National Council on Alcoholism., 1979-1980. (Box 243, Folder 10)
    - Alphabet bomber., 1980. (Box 243, Folder 11)
    - American Psychiatric Association., 1969, 1978. (Box 243, Folder 12)
    - Anti-semitism., 1980. (Box 243, Folder 13)
    - Armenians., 1980. (Box 243, Folder 14)
    - Army experiments., 1975, 1979. (Box 243, Folder 15)
    - Arson., 1980. (Box 243, Folder 16)
    - "Articles of general interest"., 1974, 1976-1979. (Box 243, Folder 17)
    - Baba Ram Dass., 1973. (Box 243, Folder 18)
    - Bahai., 1981-1982. (Box 243, Folder 19)
    - Bakke, Allan., 1979. (Box 243, Folder 20)
    - Behavior modification., 1974. (Box 243, Folder 21)
    - Bianchi, Kenneth., 1979-1982. (Box 243, Folder 22)
      See also "Hillside Strangler"
    - Bishop, Jesse Walter., 1979. (Box 243, Folder 23)
    - Black Hebrew., 1980. (Box 243, Folder 24)
    - Black Panthers., 1974, 1979-1980. (Box 243, Folder 25)
    - Board-and-care homes., 1973. (Box 243, Folder 26)
    - Bonham, John., 1980. (Box 244, Folder 1)
    - Bonin, William G.., 1980-1982. (Box 244, Folder 2)
      See also "Freeway Killer"
    - Bracho, Humberto., 1975. (Box 244, Folder 3)
    - Brainwashing/Mind control., 1977. (Box 244, Folder 4)
    - Burnout., 1983. (Box 244, Folder 5)
    - California., 1975. (Box 244, Folder 6)
    - Center for Feeling Therapy., 1981. (Box 244, Folder 7)
    - CIA., 1977-1978. (Box 244, Folder 8)
    - Child abuse., 1980. (Box 244, Folder 9)
    - China--Birth rate., undated. (Box 244, Folder 10)
    - Civil rights., 1980. (Box 244, Folder 11)
    - Colombia--Guerrillas., 1980. (Box 244, Folder 12)
    - Colson, Charles Wendell., 1980. (Box 244, Folder 13)
    - Consent., 1979-1980. (Box 244, Folder 14)
    - Corona, Juan V.., 1981-1982. (Box 244, Folder 15)
    - Cowboy., 1981. (Box 244, Folder 16)
    - Crime., 1975, 1979, 1981-1982. (Box 244, Folder 17)
    - Crime--Juvenile delinquency., 1972. (Box 244, Folder 18)
      See also "Youth crime"
    - Cults., 1967, 1974, 1976, 1978-1983. (Box 244, Folder 19)
    - Cyprus., 1974. (Box 244, Folder 20)
    - Davis, Angela., 1980. (Box 244, Folder 21)
    - Death and dying., 1979-1980. (Box 244, Folder 22)
    - Death penalty., 1976-1977, 1979-1982. (Box 244, Folder 23)
    - Dederich, Charles., 1979-1980. (Box 244, Folder 24)
      See also "Synanon"
    - Defense Department (United States)., 1979. (Box 244, Folder 25)
    - Deprogramming., 1977, 1979-1980. (Box 244, Folder 26)
    - Diet., 1972. (Box 244, Folder 27)
    - Drew, Charles R. Postgraduate Medical School., 1980. (Box 244, Folder 28)
    - Drugs and drug abuse., 1973-1975, 1978-1980. (Box 244, Folder 29)
    - Drunk driving., 1980. (Box 244, Folder 30)
    - Electroshock therapy (ECT)., 1974, 1980. (Box 244, Folder 31)
    - Faculty., 1977, 1980-1981. (Box 244, Folder 32)
    - Freeway Killer., 1980-1981. (Box 244, Folder 33)
      See also "Bonin, William G."
    - Fundamentalists., 1982. (Box 244, Folder 34)
    - Gacy, John W.., 1980. (Box 244, Folder 35)
    - Gangs., 1980. (Box 244, Folder 36)
    - Gender., 1980. (Box 244, Folder 37)
    - Genetic research and genetic therapy., 1980. (Box 244, Folder 38)
    - Gilmore, Gary Mark., 1976. (Box 244, Folder 39)
    - Golabek, Mona., undated. (Box 244, Folder 40)
    - Hare Krishna., 1976, 1979-1981. (Box 244, Folder 41)
    - Health System., 1976. (Box 245, Folder 1)
    - Hearst, Patricia., 1980-1981. (Box 245, Folder 2)
    - Hell's Angels., 1979-1980. (Box 245, Folder 3)
    - Heston, Lydia and Charlton., 1980. (Box 245, Folder 4)
    - Hillside Strangler., 1979-1980. (Box 245, Folder 5)
      See also "Bianchi, Kenneth"
    - Hinckley, John W.., 1981-1982. (Box 245, Folder 6)
    - Hoffman, Abbie., 1980. (Box 245, Folder 7)
    - Homeless., 1981. (Box 245, Folder 8)
    - Homosexuality., 1979-1980. (Box 245, Folder 9)
    - Honduras--Revolutionary Union of the People., 1980. (Box 245, Folder 10)
    - Hospice., 1980. (Box 245, Folder 11)
    - Hostages., 1980-1981, 1983. (Box 245, Folder 12)
      See also "Iran hostages"
    - Hypnosis., 1980. (Box 245, Folder 13)
    - Immigration., 1979. (Box 245, Folder 14)
    - IQ tests., 1980. (Box 245, Folder 15)
    - Iran hostages (1 of 2)., 1979-1982. (Box 245, Folder 16)
    - Iran hostages (2 of 2)., 1979-1982. (Box 245, Folder 17)
    - Jail., 1974, 1980. (Box 245, Folder 18)
    - "Jesus freaks"., 1979. (Box 245, Folder 19)
    - Jews for Jesus., 1983. (Box 245, Folder 20)
    - Jordan, Vernon E. assassination., 1980. (Box 245, Folder 21)
    - Judges., 1980. (Box 245, Folder 22)
    - Kennedy, John F., Robert F. Kennedy, and Martin Luther King Jr. assassinations., 1978-1981. (Box 245, Folder 23)
      See also "Oswald, Lee Harvey"
    - Ku Klux Klan., 1979-1980. (Box 245, Folder 24)
    - Lane, Mark., 1979. (Box 245, Folder 25)
    - Lennon, John assassination., 1980-1981. (Box 245, Folder 26)
    - Lobotomies., 1980. (Box 246, Folder 1)
    - LSD., 1978, 1980. (Box 246, Folder 2)
    - Marijuana., 1974, 1977-1981. (Box 246, Folder 3)
    - Mark-Age Inc.., 1981. (Box 246, Folder 4)
    - Meditation., 1975, 1977-1978, 1980. (Box 246, Folder 5)
    - Mental health--Laws and treatment., 1971-1972, 1980. (Box 246, Folder 6)
    - Mental illness--Insanity and criminal insanity., 1957, 1975, 1978. (Box 246, Folder 7)
    - Mesmer, Franz., 1980. (Box 246, Folder 8)
    - Milk, Harvey and George Moscone killings., 1978-1981. (Box 246, Folder 9)
    - Moluccan terrorism., 1977, 1979. (Box 246, Folder 10)
    - Moore, Sara Jane., 1975-1976, 1979. (Box 246, Folder 11)
    - Murder., 1973-1976, 1979-1981. (Box 246, Folder 12)
    - Murder--"Moulded to Murder"., 1980. (Box 246, Folder 13)
    - Murderers--Legal/Insanity., 1978-1979. (Box 246, Folder 14)
    - "Names in the news"., 1979. (Box 246, Folder 15)
    - Nazis., 1979. (Box 246, Folder 16)
    - Neuroanatomy., 1943, 1950, 1958. (Box 246, Folder 17)
      Contains published books and pamphlets, including A.T. Rasmussen, Outlines of Neuro-Anatomy; Louis Hausman, Atlas of the Spinal Cord and Brainstem and the Forebrain; John T. Manter, Essentials of Clinical Neuroanatomy and Neurophysiology; Frank H. Netter and Gerhardt von Bonin, Functional Neuroanatomy; and Wendell J.S. Krieg, A Polychrome Atlas of the Brain Stem. Some items contain notes, presumably by LJW.
    - Neuropsychiatric Institute (UCLA)--Historical., 1958, 1974. (Box 246, Folder 18)
    - Neurosurgery., 1968, 1971, 1973. (Box 246, Folder 19)
    - Nursing homes--Patient care., 1983. (Box 246, Folder 20)
    - Obesity., undated. (Box 246, Folder 21)
    - Oklahoma Supreme Court--Ed Edmonson., undated. (Box 246, Folder 22)
    - Oswald, Lee Harvey., 1975, 1977, 1981. (Box 246, Folder 23)
      See also "Kennedy, John F., Robert F. Kennedy, and Martin Luther King Jr. assassinations"
    - People's Temple., 1979-1981. (Box 246, Folder 24)
    - People's Temple--Larry Layton., 1980-1982. (Box 246, Folder 25)
    - Political assassinations., 1967. (Box 246, Folder 26)
      Contains John Kaplan, "The Assassins."
    - Political prisoners., 1982. (Box 247, Folder 1)
    - Political unrest., undated. (Box 247, Folder 2)
    - Prisoners of war (POW)., 1981. (Box 247, Folder 3)
    - Prisons., 1973, 1977, 1980. (Box 247, Folder 4)
    - Pritikin diet., undated. (Box 247, Folder 5)
    - Progressive Labor Party (PLP)., 1974. (Box 247, Folder 6)
    - Project CHEER., 1980. (Box 247, Folder 7)
    - Psychiatry., 1973-1974, 1978. (Box 247, Folder 8)
    - Psychiatry--Legal., 1964-1966, 1980. (Box 247, Folder 9)
    - Psychobiology., 1980. (Box 247, Folder 10)
    - Psychosurgery., 1969, 1973, 1979-1980. (Box 247, Folder 11)
    - Psychotherapy., 1972-1973, 1980. (Box 247, Folder 12)
    - Racism., 1974. (Box 247, Folder 13)
    - Radical politics., 1974-1976, 1979-1980. (Box 247, Folder 14)
    - Rajneesh, Bhagwan Shree., 1982. (Box 247, Folder 15)
    - Rebirthing., 1980. (Box 247, Folder 16)
    - Rehabilitation of criminals., 1974-1975. (Box 247, Folder 17)
    - Religious groups--Fraud., 1980. (Box 247, Folder 18)
    - Right to die., 1980. (Box 247, Folder 19)
    - River of Life., 1981. (Box 247, Folder 20)
    - Rentzel, Lance., 1974. (Box 247, Folder 21)
    - Rubin, Jerry., 1980. (Box 247, Folder 22)
    - Rucker, William Elliott., 1980. (Box 247, Folder 23)
    - Santa Fe prison riot (New Mexico State Penitentiary)., 1980. (Box 247, Folder 24)
    - Scientology., 1979-1981, 1983. (Box 247, Folder 25)
    - Serious crime., undated. (Box 247, Folder 26)
    - Sex offenders., 1975. (Box 247, Folder 27)
    - Sexuality., 1970-1971, 1979. (Box 247, Folder 28)
    - Shame., 1976. (Box 247, Folder 29)
    - Shockley, William., 1974. (Box 247, Folder 30)
    - Siblings., 1980. (Box 247, Folder 31)
    - Skid Row Stabber., 1979-1980. (Box 247, Folder 32)
    - Smoking., 1978. (Box 247, Folder 33)
    - Smoke detectors., 1980. (Box 247, Folder 34)
    - Snyder, Arthur K.., 1980. (Box 247, Folder 35)
    - Son of Sam (David Berkowitz)., 1977. (Box 247, Folder 36)
    - South Africa., 1977, 1979-1980, 1984. (Box 247, Folder 37)
    - Soviet Union., 1981. (Box 247, Folder 38)
    - Stress., 1980-1981. (Box 247, Folder 39)
    - Substance abuse., 1979-1983. (Box 247, Folder 40)
      Includes publications California Society for the Treatment of Alcoholism and Other Drug Dependencies News, Substance Abuse: A Publication of the Association for Medical Education and Research in Substance Abuse and the Career Teacher Program in Alcohol and Drug Abuse, Department of Alcohol and Drug Programs Alcohol and Drug Program Activities, Focus on Alcohol and Drugs Issues.
    - Suicide., 1970, 1976, 1980-1981. (Box 247, Folder 41)
    - Survivalists., 1981. (Box 247, Folder 42)
    - Synanon., 1978-1981. (Box 247, Folder 43)
    - Television and telecommunications., 1973-1974, 1976. (Box 247, Folder 44)
    - Tenure., 1975. (Box 247, Folder 45)
    - Terrorism., 1976, 1980-1981. (Box 247, Folder 46)
    - Thomas, Dylan., 1980. (Box 247, Folder 47)
    - Tourette's Syndrome., 1980. (Box 247, Folder 48)
    - Unification Church., 1979-1982. (Box 247, Folder 49)
    - United Nations., 1974. (Box 247, Folder 50)
    - Vampirism., 1974. (Box 247, Folder 51)
    - Van Houten, Leslie., 1980. (Box 247, Folder 52)
    - Veterans., 1979, 1981. (Box 248, Folder 1)
    - Violence., 1973-1976, 1978-1982. (Box 248, Folder 2)
      See also "Television and telecommunications"
    - Violence--"Violence in American Life Conference," Center for the Study of Democratic Institutions and California Commission on Crime Control and Violence Prevention (1 of 2)., 1981 June. (Box 248, Folder 3)
    - Violence--"Violence in American Life Conference," Center for the Study of Democratic Institutions and California Commission on Crime Control and Violence Prevention (2 of 2)., 1981 June. (Box 248, Folder 4)
    - Violence--UCLA Center for the Study and Reduction of Violence., 1973-1975. (Box 248, Folder 5)
      See also CSRV subsection under "Academic Career."
    - Watson, Charles (Tex)., 1980. (Box 248, Folder 6)
    - Weather Underground., 1979-1980. (Box 248, Folder 7)
    - Women's Christian Temperance Union (WCTU)., 1980. (Box 248, Folder 8)
    - Workplace., 1980. (Box 248, Folder 9)
    - Worldwide Church of God., 1979-1980. (Box 248, Folder 10)
    - Yorkshire Ripper., 1980-1981. (Box 248, Folder 11)
    - Youth crime., 1974, 1979. (Box 248, Folder 12)
      See also "Crime--Juvenile delinquency"
    - Zebra Killings., 1979. (Box 248, Folder 13)
    - Labels for news clippings folders., undated. (Box 248, Folder 14)
- Restricted Materials
  - Hearst, Patricia Campbell--Notes, articles, and correspondence related to LJW's report., 1962, 1974-1976. (Box 250, Folder 1)
  - Hearst, Patricia Campbell--LJW's book "A Different Person," Section II: Follow- up examinations by LJW., 1976 February 24. (Box 250, Folder 2)
    Folder contains "Report of Psychiatric Re-Examination of Patricia Campbell Hearst" by LJW.
  - Hearst, Patricia Campbell--LJW's book "A Different Person," Section II: Follow- up examinations by Margaret Singer., 1975 October 8-1976 March 30. (Box 250, Folder 3)
  - Hearst, Patricia Campbell-- "Tania Interview"., ca. 1974-1975. (Box 250, Folder 4)
    An manuscript drafted by Hearst and SLA members, the Harrises, while they were in hiding.
  - Hearst, Patricia Campbell--Working drafts of psychiatric examination (Folder 1 of 3)., 1974-1976. (Box 250, Folder 5)
  - Hearst, Patricia Campbell--Working drafts of psychiatric examination (Folder 2 of 3)., 1974-1976. (Box 250, Folder 6)
  - Hearst, Patricia Campbell--Working drafts of psychiatric examination (Folder 3 of 3)., 1974-1976. (Box 250, Folder 7)
  - Hearst, Patricia Campbell--Transcripts and notes from interviews with P. Hearst., 1975-1976. (Box 250, Folder 8)
    Includes partial transcript of Interview #3.
  - Hearst, Patricia Campbell--Psychiatric report, information about jurors, notes, letters to Patricia/Tania.., 1975-1977. (Box 250, Folder 9)
    Includes letters addressed to Patricia/Tania from the New Dawn Party and others in "the movement."
  - Hearst, Patricia Campbell--Material drafted for book., 1976 February-September. (Box 251, Folder 1)
    *Psychological reports from LJW and MTS
  - Hearst, Patricia Campbell--"Report of Psychiatric Examination" working drafts (Folder 1 of 5)., 1975. (Box 251, Folder 2)
    Report by LJW and Margaret Thaler Singer, Ph.D.
  - Hearst, Patricia Campbell--"Report of Psychiatric Examination" working drafts (Folder 2 of 5)., 1975. (Box 251, Folder 3)
  - Hearst, Patricia Campbell--"Report of Psychiatric Examination" working drafts (Folder 3 of 5)., 1975. (Box 251, Folder 4)
  - Hearst, Patricia Campbell--"Report of Psychiatric Examination" working drafts (Folder 4 of 5)., 1975. (Box 251, Folder 5)
  - Hearst, Patricia Campbell--"Report of Psychiatric Examination" working drafts (Folder 5 of 5)., 1975. (Box 251, Folder 6)
  - Hearst, Patricia Campbell--"Report of Psychiatric Examination" original typed copy (Folder 1 of 3)., 1975 October 24. (Box 251, Folder 7)
  - Hearst, Patricia Campbell--"Report of Psychiatric Examination" original typed copy (Folder 2 of 3)., 1975 October 24. (Box 251, Folder 8)
  - Hearst, Patricia Campbell--"Report of Psychiatric Examination" original typed copy (Folder 3 of 3)., 1975 October 24. (Box 252, Folder 1)
  - Hearst, Patricia Campbell--"Report of Psychiatric Examination" (Folder 1 of 2)., 1975 October 24. (Box 252, Folder 2)
  - Hearst, Patricia Campbell--"Report of Psychiatric Examination" (Folder 2 of 2)., 1975 October 24, 1976 February 24. (Box 252, Folder 3)
    Report by LJW and Margaret Thaler Singer, Ph.D. and footnotes.
  - Hearst, Patricia Campbell--Transcripts of LJW's notes from Interview 1 with P. Hearst., 1975 September 30. (Box 252, Folder 4)
    September 30, 1975, 3:30 PM (Notes dictated by LJW).
  - Hearst, Patricia Campbell--Transcripts of Interview 2 with P. Hearst., 1975 September 30. (Box 252, Folder 5)
    September 30, 1975, 7:30-9:30 PM.
  - Hearst, Patricia Campbell--Transcripts of Interview 3 with P. Hearst., 1975 October 2. (Box 252, Folder 6)
    October 2, 1975, 2:30 PM.
  - Hearst, Patricia Campbell--Transcripts of Interview 4 with P. Hearst., 1975 October 3. (Box 252, Folder 7)
    October 3, 1975, 2:00 PM.
  - Hearst, Patricia Campbell--Transcripts of Interview 5 with P. Hearst., 1975 October 4. (Box 252, Folder 8)
    October 4, 1975, 8:00 PM.
  - Hearst, Patricia Campbell--Transcripts of Interview 6 with P. Hearst., 1975 October 5. (Box 252, Folder 9)
    October 5, 1975, 9:00 PM.
  - Hearst, Patricia Campbell--Transcripts of Interview 7 with P. Hearst., 1975 October 10. (Box 252, Folder 10)
    October 10, 1975, 9:30 PM.
  - Hearst, Patricia Campbell--Transcripts of Interview 8 with P. Hearst., 1975 October 11. (Box 252, Folder 11)
    October 11, 1975, 9:30 AM.
  - Hearst, Patricia Campbell--Transcripts of Interview 9 with P. Hearst., 1975 October 11. (Box 252, Folder 12)
    October 11, 1975, 2:15 PM. Trish Tobin present for part of interview.
  - Hearst, Patricia Campbell--Transcripts of Interview 10 with P. Hearst., 1975 October 11. (Box 252, Folder 13)
    October 11, 1975, 8:25 PM.
  - Hearst, Patricia Campbell--Transcript of "LJW and Margaret T. Singer Thoughts"., 1975 October 1. (Box 252, Folder 14)
  - Hearst, Patricia Campbell--Transcript of "LJW and Margaret T. Singer Thoughts"., 1975 October 2. (Box 252, Folder 15)
    Recorded at 7:30 PM.
  - Hearst, Patricia Campbell-- Margaret T. Singer notes and transcripts., 1975 September 27-October 16. (Box 253, Folder 1)